"subject_str","subject_id","subject_type","predicate_org","predicate","object_str","object_id","object_type","text"
"thawne","Thawne","PERSON","becomes","become","the reverse-flash","the Reverse-Flash","PERSON","Still seeking to spend time with the Flash and be his friend , Thawne becomes the Reverse-Flash , vowing to making Barry 's life a living hell until he learns to `` make time '' for him ."
"isma'il ibn ahmad","Isma'il ibn Ahmad","PERSON","is ruler from","be ruler from","samanid","Samanid","NORP","Bal'ami is first mentioned as serving under the Samanid ruler Isma'il ibn Ahmad , and was later appointed as vizier by the latter 's grandson , Nasr II ."
"rick kuhn","Rick Kuhn","PERSON","is center of","be center of","boston college","http://www.wikidata.org/entity/Q49118","Language","Hill and two Pittsburgh gamblers set up the 1978–79 Boston College basketball point-shaving scheme by convincing Boston College center Rick Kuhn to participate ."
"lynch","Lynch","PERSON","attended","attend","boylan catholic high school","Boylan Catholic High School","ORG","Lynch attended Boylan Catholic High School , where she was on the student council ."
"galileo","Galileo","WORK_OF_ART","observed","observe","the milky way","the Milky Way","LOC","Galileo observed the Milky Way , previously believed to be nebulous , and found it to be a multitude of stars packed so densely that they appeared from Earth to be clouds ."
"f. d. hole","F. D. Hole","PERSON","widely performed","widely perform","the antigo silt loam song","the Antigo Silt Loam Song","WORK_OF_ART","F. D. Hole wrote and widely performed the Antigo Silt Loam Song , whose melody and lyrics illustrated and celebrated the features , geography , and natural history of Wisconsin soils , entertaining audiences and appealing to students of all ages ."
"clynes","Clynes","ORG","gave a concert playing","give a concert play","the beethoven diabelli variations","the Beethoven Diabelli Variations","WORK_OF_ART","During his three years at UCSD , in La Jolla , Clynes gave a concert at Brubecker Hall , playing the Beethoven Diabelli Variations , as well as a first performance of a group of 5 songs he composed , called `` Sentone Songs , '' employing the remarkable vocal range of Linda Vickerman who performed them ."
"einstein","Einstein","PERSON","visited","visit","america","America","GPE","In December 1930 , Einstein visited America for the second time , originally intended as a two-month working visit as a research fellow at the California Institute of Technology ."
"rafael jordana butticaz","http://www.wikidata.org/entity/Q21339046","Person","born","bear","zaragoza","Zaragoza","GPE","Rafael Jordana Butticaz ( born Zaragoza , 17 July 1941 ) is a Spanish scientist , Emeritus Professor of Animal Physiology and Zoology , and specialist in springtails ( Collembola ) ."
"dirac","Dirac","PRODUCT","told","tell","abraham pais","Abraham Pais","PERSON","In 1928 , building on 2×2 spin matrices which he purported to have discovered independently of Wolfgang Pauli 's work on non-relativistic spin systems ( Dirac told Abraham Pais , `` I believe I got these [ matrices ] independently of Pauli and possibly Pauli got these independently of me . `` ) ,"
"spider-man","Spider-Man","PERSON","Loves","Loves","mary jane","Mary Jane","PERSON","`` Spider-Man Loves Mary Jane '' ."
"doctor manhattan","Doctor Manhattan","ORG","kills","kill","pandora","Pandora","PERSON","Doctor Manhattan then kills Pandora after she finally realizes that he was the one responsible for all of the sins for which she had been blamed ."
"cecil spring rice","Cecil Spring Rice","PERSON","is the British ambassador to","be the British ambassador to","the united states","the United States","GPE","During the First World War , Pupin met with Cecil Spring Rice , the British ambassador to the United States , in an attempt to aid Austro-Hungarian Slavs in Canadian custody ."
"filmer","Filmer","ORG","won","win","a government exhibition scholarship","a Government Exhibition Scholarship","WORK_OF_ART","Filmer spent his early life in Western Australia and won a Government Exhibition Scholarship which took him to the University of Melbourne from which he graduated B.V.Sc ."
"world war ii","World War II","EVENT","broke out","break out","australia","Australia","GPE","He and his family returned to Australia when World War II broke out , he returned to the Veterinary school at the University of Sydney ."
"xavier","Xavier","ORG","leaves","leave","the x-men","the X-Men","PERSON","Xavier is left without his telepathy and , overcome with guilt , leaves the X-Men and is incarcerated for his actions ."
"nambiar","Nambiar","PERSON","is As the founder chairman of","be As the founder chairman of","keltron","KELTRON","ORG","As the founder chairman of Keltron , Nambiar was instrumental in taking electronics to the villages by setting up 50 women 's co-operatives that produced most of the company 's consumer products ."
"xavier","Xavier","ORG","mentally fights","mentally fight","exodus","Exodus","PERSON","Exodus tries to heal Xavier , Xavier mentally fights Exodus ."
"godwin","Godwin","ORG","is a member of","be a member of","the american physical society","the American Physical Society","ORG","Godwin is a member of the American Physical Society , the Ninety-Nines , Inc. , Association of Space Explorers , Aircraft Owners and Pilots Association ."
"katherine lodgen sexton","Katherine Lodgen Sexton","PERSON","is a graduate of","be a graduate of","the nyu school of law","The NYU School of Law","ORG","Sexton 's younger child is Katherine Lodgen Sexton , a graduate of Yale and the NYU School of Law ."
"pasternak","Pasternak","PERSON","sought exile in Britain joining","seek exile in Britain join","eliot trevor oakeshott slater","Eliot Trevor Oakeshott Slater","PERSON","Pasternak sought exile in Britain , joining Eliot Trevor Oakeshott Slater , a psychiatrist she had met in Munich ."
"exodus","Exodus","PRODUCT","to heal","to heal","xavier","Xavier","ORG","Exodus tries to heal Xavier , Xavier mentally fights Exodus ."
"the ninth doctor","the Ninth Doctor","WORK_OF_ART","is an incarnation of","be a incarnation of","the doctor","The Doctor","WORK_OF_ART","The Ninth Doctor is an incarnation of the Doctor , the protagonist of the BBC science fiction television programme `` Doctor Who '' ."
"venus","Venus","PERSON","is ex-wife from","be ex - wife from","sivana","Sivana","ORG","Beautia and Magnificus Sivana are reintroduced again in this series ; their mother , Sivana 's ex-wife Venus , is briefly seen in `` The Power of Shazam ! '' #"
"deathstroke","Deathstroke","PERSON","to kill","to kill","ryan choi","http://www.wikidata.org/entity/Q4817193","Person","The team also includes the shrinking killer , Dwarfstar , who recently hired Deathstroke and his to kill Ryan Choi ."
"xavier","Xavier","ORG","mentally fights","mentally fight","exodus","Exodus","PRODUCT","Exodus tries to heal Xavier , Xavier mentally fights Exodus ."
"deetz","Deetz","GPE","attended","attend","ohio university","Ohio University","ORG","Deetz attended Ohio University for both his M.A . ( 1972 ) and his Ph.D. ( 1973 ) in Communication , both under the advisement of Kenneth Williams ."
"nobel","Nobel","WORK_OF_ART","was a student in","be a student in","uppsala","Uppsala","GPE","At the time , Nobel was a student in Uppsala , but also helped in the factory ."
"longuski","Longuski","PERSON","co-inventor with","co - inventor with","dan javorsek","Dan Javorsek","PERSON","Longuski is co-inventor with Dan Javorsek of a `` Method of Velocity Precision Pointing in Spin-Stabilized Spacecraft or Rockets '' ."
"the high evolutionary","the High Evolutionary","LOC","helped to restore","help to restore","the savage land","the Savage Land","WORK_OF_ART","The High Evolutionary once helped to restore the Savage Land and its inhabitants after the engines that kept the volcanoes active were demolished by Terminus ."
"daniel attinger","http://www.wikidata.org/entity/Q56862498","Person","is","be","researcher","http://www.wikidata.org/entity/Q1650915","Profession","Daniel Attinger is a mechanical engineer , researcher and an academic ."
"durock","Durock","PERSON","continued playing the character along with playing","continue play the character along with play","the swamp thing","the Swamp Thing","PERSON","Durock continued playing the character in the 1990 television series along with playing the Swamp Thing ."
"actors","http://www.wikidata.org/entity/Q10798782","Profession","portrayed","portray","the doctor","http://www.wikidata.org/entity/Q34358","Person","James Delingpole of `` The Spectator '' noted that subsequent to Fourth Doctor Tom Baker 's departure and prior to Eccleston , actors who portrayed the Doctor had a tendency to play the role `` too camp , knowing , lovable or twee '' ."
"sivana","Sivana","NORP","attempted to destroy respectively","attempt to destroy respectively","captain marvel","Captain Marvel","PRODUCT","Beautia 's remaining siblings include the super-strong Magnificus , and evil teenagers Georgia and Thaddeus Sivana , Jr. As the Sivana Family , Sivana , Georgia , and Sivana Jr. attempted to destroy Captain Marvel , Mary Marvel , and Captain Marvel Jr. , respectively ."
"beast","Beast","PERSON","cures","cure","the legacy virus","the Legacy Virus","PRODUCT","As Beast cures the Legacy Virus , many infected Genoshan mutants recover overnight , providing Magneto , the current ruler of Genosha , with an army to start the third World War ."
"andrei gennadievich aleksenko","Andrei Gennadievich Aleksenko","PERSON","was","be","professor","http://www.wikidata.org/entity/Q37226","Profession","Andrei Gennadievich Aleksenko ( ; born 24 January 1934 — 7 April 2014 ) was a Russian scientist , professor and a specialist in the field of microcircuitry technology ."
"tillson","Tillson","PERSON","was","be","a girl scout","a Girl Scout","PRODUCT","Tillson was a Girl Scout ."
"bridges","Bridges","PERSON","married","marry","gertrude ives","Gertrude Ives","PERSON","Bridges married Gertrude Ives , with whom he had four children ."
"joseph p. hurley","Joseph P. Hurley","PERSON","is the Bishop of","be the Bishop of","st. augustine","St. Augustine","GPE","In 1963 he served as a `` peritus '' ( expert adviser ) to the Bishop of St. Augustine , Joseph P. Hurley , at the Second Vatican Council ."
"young","Young","PERSON","opposed","oppose","the vietnam war","the Vietnam War","EVENT","Young opposed the Vietnam War , helped enact legislation that established the U.S. Institute for Peace , established the Chattahoochee River National Recreation Area and negotiated federal funds for MARTA and the Atlanta Highways ."
"killer frost","Killer Frost","WORK_OF_ART","battles","battle","team flash","Team Flash","PRODUCT","Joining Savitar as his enforcer , Killer Frost battles Team Flash ."
"britain","Britain","GPE","should join","should join","the north american free trade area","the North American Free Trade Area","ORG","She argued that Britain should renegotiate its terms of membership or else leave the EU and join the North American Free Trade Area ."
"margarita ratsenskaya","Margarita Ratsenskaya","PERSON","is wife","be wife","anokhin","Anokhin","PERSON","Mironov 's flight instructor was Margarita Ratsenskaya , the aero-club 's gliding squad commander and Anokhin 's wife ."
"wilfrid israel","Wilfrid Israel","PERSON","visiting","visit","india","India","GPE","Sundaram was Gandhi 's disciple and special envoy , whom Wilfrid Israel met while visiting India and visiting the Indian leader 's home in 1925 ."
"magneto","Magneto","PERSON","is the current ruler of","be the current ruler of","genosha","Genosha","GPE","As Beast cures the Legacy Virus , many infected Genoshan mutants recover overnight , providing Magneto , the current ruler of Genosha , with an army to start the third World War ."
"gallwas","Gallwas","ORG","is a native of","be a native of","california","California","GPE","Gallwas , a native of California , first showed an interest in climbing in junior high school ."
"sandra cardosa-zinker","Sandra Cardosa-Zinker","PERSON","is therapist of","be therapist of","gestalt","Gestalt","PRODUCT","With his wife , Gestalt therapist Sandra Cardosa-Zinker , he published several articles about couples therapy ."
"zyornova","Zyornova","PERSON","a Secretary of","a Secretary of","the russian student christian movement","the Russian Student Christian Movement","ORG","From 1925 to 1932 , Zyornova was a Secretary of the Russian Student Christian Movement in Paris ."
"the tenth doctor","http://www.wikidata.org/entity/Q2656347","Person","is an incarnation of","be a incarnation of","the doctor","http://www.wikidata.org/entity/Q34358","Person","The Tenth Doctor is an incarnation of the Doctor , the protagonist of the BBC science fiction television programme `` Doctor Who '' ."
"jutte zarniko","Jutte Zarniko","PERSON","is the sister of","be the sister of","barbara zarniko","Barbara Zarniko","PERSON","He married Jutte Zarniko , the sister of Barbara Zarniko , one of Franz Simon 's students in 1932 ."
"chandradathan","Chandradathan","PERSON","his career by joining","his career by join","the indian space research organization","the Indian Space Research Organization","ORG","Chandradathan started his career in 1972 , by joining the Indian Space Research Organization ( ISRO ) where he worked for the SLV-3 project , the development of solid propellant formulations ."
"rosalind hauk","Rosalind Hauk","PERSON","is a PhD student at","be a PhD student at","washington university","http://www.wikidata.org/entity/Q777403","Language","In 1959 , he married Rosalind Hauk , a PhD student at Washington University ."
"alistair smythe","http://www.wikidata.org/entity/Q2837209","Person","is an associate of","be a associate of","norman osborn","Norman Osborn","PERSON","In the `` House of M '' reality , a furious J. Jonah Jameson hired Alistair Smythe , an associate of Norman Osborn , to build a Spider-Slayer to get revenge against the Parkers ."
"marston","Marston","PERSON","created","create","doctor psycho","http://www.wikidata.org/entity/Q5287377","Person","Marston , a psychologist , created Doctor Psycho as a murderous psychopath with an intense hatred of women ."
"suggate","Suggate","ORG","joined","join","the new zealand geological survey","the New Zealand Geological Survey","ORG","Emigrating to New Zealand in 1947 , Suggate joined the New Zealand Geological Survey ."
"james shaw","James Shaw","PERSON","is the Climate Change Minister in","be the Climate Change Minister in","the new zealand government","the New Zealand Government","ORG","On Wednesday 10 December 2020 , members of the Intergenerational Climate Ambassadors group , including Salinger , met with James Shaw , the Climate Change Minister in the New Zealand government ."
"bill clinton","Bill Clinton","PERSON","is President of of","be President of of","the united states","the United States","GPE","In 1999 , President of the United States Bill Clinton nominated Delaney to be Assistant Secretary of the Air Force ( Acquisition ) ."
"robert rapoport","Robert Rapoport","PERSON","is","be","social anthropologist","http://www.wikidata.org/entity/Q66581878","Profession","After her training in 1957 , Rhona married Robert Rapoport , social anthropologist ."
"alice p. gast","Alice P. Gast","PERSON","is president of","be president of","lehigh university","Lehigh University","ORG","A panel was created , chaired by Alice P. Gast , president of Lehigh University ."
"bill clinton","Bill Clinton","PERSON","is the President of","be the President of","the united states","the United States","GPE","The following year she was nominated by the President of the United States , Bill Clinton and confirmed by the United States Senate as the fourth Assistant Secretary for the Department of Energy ( DOE ) Office of Environmental Management ."
"georgy pavlov","Georgy Pavlov","PERSON","is predecessor of","be predecessor of","kruchina","Kruchina","PERSON","Kruchina 's predecessor , Georgy Pavlov , died the same way as Kruchina did , on October 6 ."
"superman","Superman","PERSON","to confront","to confront","doctor psycho","Doctor Psycho","WORK_OF_ART","Superman , Question , and the others arrive in Pittsburgh to confront Doctor Psycho ."
"ludovico gonzaga","Ludovico Gonzaga","PERSON","is the ruler of","be the ruler of","mantua","Mantua","GPE","Alberti is said to appear in Mantegna 's great frescoes in the Camera degli Sposi , as the older man dressed in dark red clothes , who whispers in the ear of Ludovico Gonzaga , the ruler of Mantua ."
"onslaught","Onslaught","WORK_OF_ART","nearly kills","nearly kill","the x-men","the X-Men","ORG","After Onslaught nearly kills the X-Men they team up with the Avengers to make a plan to stop him , knowing full well that it may come down to them killing Xavier if the world is to survive ."
"phantom stranger","Phantom Stranger","WORK_OF_ART","revives","revive","terrance","Terrance","PERSON","Phantom Stranger revives Terrance by stabbing the latter 's body with Zalkoat 's sword ."
"the green goblin","The Green Goblin","PERSON","holds her hostage to bait","hold her hostage to bait","spider-man","Spider-Man","PERSON","When the Green Goblin kidnaps Gwen and holds her hostage to bait Spider-Man , Sheldon frantically follows the resulting chase in a taxi and witnesses her death ."
"rose tyler","Rose Tyler","PERSON","asks","ask","the doctor","The Doctor","PERSON","This is addressed in `` Rose '' when Rose Tyler asks the Doctor , `` If you 're an alien , how come you sound like you 're from the North ? `` ,"
"regional coordinator","Regional Coordinator","ORG","is volunteer of","be volunteer of","seti league","SETI League","ORG","Tough was a SETI League Charter Member , edited the online academic journal `` Contact in Context '' , initiated that journal 's Best Ideas Awards , was founding chair of the SETI League 's Strategic Planning Committee , and served as a SETI League volunteer Regional Coordinator ."
"hal jordan","Hal Jordan","PERSON","is Lantern of","be Lantern of","green","Green","LOC","The Swamp Thing is among the heroes who attend a memorial service for Green Lantern Hal Jordan ."
"ann doerr","Ann Doerr","PERSON","is the wife of","be the wife of","john doerr","John Doerr","PERSON","Khan subsequently received sponsorship from Ann Doerr , the wife of John Doerr ."
"leon theremin","http://www.wikidata.org/entity/Q333265","Person","born","bear","lev sergeyevich termen","Lev Sergeyevich Termen","PERSON","Leon Theremin ( born Lev Sergeyevich Termen ; – 3 November 1993 ) was a Russian and Soviet inventor , most famous for his invention of the theremin , one of the first electronic musical instruments and the first to be mass-produced ."
"panini comics","Panini Comics","ORG","bought","buy","marvel uk","Marvel UK","ORG","Panini Comics bought Marvel UK and in 2006 renewed and broadened their licence with Marvel which allows them to produce original comic stories for the British and European markets ."
"sivana","Sivana","PERSON","attempted to destroy respectively","attempt to destroy respectively","captain marvel","Captain Marvel","PRODUCT","Beautia 's remaining siblings include the super-strong Magnificus , and evil teenagers Georgia and Thaddeus Sivana , Jr. As the Sivana Family , Sivana , Georgia , and Sivana Jr. attempted to destroy Captain Marvel , Mary Marvel , and Captain Marvel Jr. , respectively ."
"kennda lynch","Kennda Lynch","PERSON","is the daughter of","be the daughter of","kenneth lynch","Kenneth Lynch","PERSON","Kennda Lynch is the daughter of Marlene Cosby and Kenneth Lynch ."
"ernest dawson hardy","Ernest Dawson Hardy","PERSON","is a civil servant at","be a civil servant at","the inland revenue","the Inland Revenue","ORG","On 16 March 1946 , she married Ernest Dawson Hardy , a civil servant at the Inland Revenue ."
"d'auvergne","D'Auvergne","PERSON","would be","would be","duke of bouillon","Duke of Bouillon","ORG","D'Auvergne was now known as the Prince of Bouillon , and would be Duke of Bouillon if Jacques Léopold de La Tour d'Auvergne died without issue ."
"elisha foote","Elisha Foote","PERSON","is a statistician in","be a statistician in","east bloomfield","East Bloomfield","GPE","On August 12 , 1841 , she married Elisha Foote , a judge , statistician , and inventor in East Bloomfield ."
"falkoff","Falkoff","PERSON","received","receive","a bachelor of engineering","a Bachelor of Engineering","ORG","Falkoff , born in New Jersey , received a Bachelor of Engineering ( B.Ch ."
"the x-men","the X-Men","ORG","managed to destroy","manage to destroy","onslaught","Onslaught","PRODUCT","Thanks to this sacrifice , the X-Men finally managed to destroy Onslaught ."
"berger","Berger","ORG","founded","found","sono-tek corporation","Sono-Tek Corporation","ORG","Berger founded Sono-Tek Corporation based on this technology and while working at the company he made contributions to the fields of combustion , semiconductor manufacturing , electronic printed circuit board manufacturing , drug eluting stents and spray drying ."
"sheetal amte","http://www.wikidata.org/entity/Q26923220","Person","was the daughter of","be the daughter of","vikas amte","Vikas Amte","PERSON","Sheetal Amte was the daughter of Vikas Amte and Bharati Amte , and granddaughter of Baba Amte , who established a rehabilitation home for lepers in Anandwan , in the state of Maharashtra , and stayed there in campus ."
"jaffee","Jaffee","PERSON","is the chair of","be the chair of","the national cancer advisory board","the National Cancer Advisory Board","ORG","Jaffee is the chair of the National Cancer Advisory Board for the National Cancer Institute , of which she has been a member since 2013 , and co-chair of the NCI `` Blue Ribbon Panel '' for the National Cancer Moonshot Initiative ."
"gretchen susan schuette","Gretchen Susan Schuette","PERSON","is the daughter of","be the daughter of","esther schuette","Esther Schuette","PERSON","Gretchen Susan Schuette , the daughter of William and Esther Schuette , was born in 1946 ."
"abbott laboratories","Abbott Laboratories","ORG","is former employer of","be former employer of","nicol","Nicol","PERSON","While she was working there , Pandex was bought by Nicol 's former employer Abbott Laboratories ."
"lynch","Lynch","ORG","was also","be also","girl scout","Girl Scout","PERSON","Lynch was also Girl Scout , including being appointed as the student delegate to the National Girl Scout Program Conference ."
"doctor light","http://www.wikidata.org/entity/Q2856301","Person","was killed","be kill","the day","the day","DATE","Later during the `` Trinity War '' storyline , Question gives Superman a newspaper clipping stating that Doctor Psycho was sighted in Khandaq the day when Doctor Light was killed ."
"gizmo","Gizmo","PERSON","is teammate of","be teammate of","psimon","http://www.wikidata.org/entity/Q5197011","Person","Psimon 's teammate Gizmo eventually broke the team out of prison , and Psimon , now acting as team leader , led the Five in kidnapping Dr. Helga Jace in order to force her to make them an army of `` Mud Men '' to aid them in their battles ."
"woronzow","Woronzow","PERSON","married","marry","agnes graham","Agnes Graham","PERSON","Woronzow married Agnes Graham but all their children died at birth or in infancy ."
"walter i. bradbury","Walter I. Bradbury","PERSON","is publisher science fiction editor of","be publisher science fiction editor of","doubleday","Doubleday","ORG","In 1949 , book publisher Doubleday 's science fiction editor Walter I. Bradbury accepted Asimov 's unpublished `` Grow Old with Me '' ( 40,000 words ) , but requested that it be extended to a full novel of 70,000 words ."
"alexander georg von humboldt","Alexander Georg von Humboldt","PERSON","is father of","be father of","humboldt","Humboldt","ORG","Humboldt 's father , Alexander Georg von Humboldt , belonged to a prominent Pomeranian family ."
"nancy huntly","http://www.wikidata.org/entity/Q56527986","Person","is a professor of","be a professor of","biology","Biology","ORG","Nancy Huntly is a professor of Biology at Utah State University , and the director of USU 's Ecology Center ."
"richards","Richards","PERSON","costarring","costarring","kirstie alley","Kirstie Alley","PERSON","Richards played the role of Frank in the sitcom `` Kirstie '' , costarring Kirstie Alley and Rhea Perlman , premiering on TV Land on December 4 , 2013 ."
"hannah moore","Hannah Moore","PERSON","is a Quaker from","be a Quaker from","philadelphia","Philadelphia","GPE","Hannah Moore , a Quaker from Philadelphia , married Peale in 1805 , becoming his third wife ."
"xavier","Xavier","FAC","to help","to help","the x-men","The X-Men","ORG","Xavier senses the changes taking place in Jean Grey , and returns to Earth to help and resume leadership of the X-Men ."
"the stream evolution model","the Stream Evolution Model","WORK_OF_ART","co-developed","co - develope","thorne","Thorne","PERSON","The stream evolution model which Thorne co-developed has been applied to the North Fork Toutle in order to classify reaches under the different stream stages set out in the model ."
"moses williams","Moses Williams","PERSON","is slave of","be slave of","peale","http://www.wikidata.org/entity/Q454945","Person","Peale 's slave , Moses Williams , was also trained in the arts while growing up in the Peale household and later became a professional silhouette artist ."
"camilloni","Camilloni","GPE","is a resident in","be a resident in","the solar geoengineering research program","the Solar Geoengineering Research Program","ORG","Camilloni is a resident in the Solar Geoengineering Research Program of Harvard University and director of the Master 's in Environmental Sciences at the Faculty of Exact and Natural Sciences of the UBA ."
"thawne","Thawne","ORG","is a forefather of","be a forefather of","thaddeus thawne","Thaddeus Thawne","PERSON","The first and most well-known character to assume the `` Reverse-Flash '' mantle , Thawne is the archnemesis of Barry Allen ( the second superhero to be called the Flash ) , a descendant of Malcolm Thawne , and a forefather of Bart Allen , Thaddeus Thawne , and Owen Mercer ."
"christopher chabris","Christopher Chabris","PERSON","derided","deride","imagine","Imagine","WORK_OF_ART","But Christopher Chabris , writing in `` The New York Times Book Review '' , derided `` Imagine '' for its `` many elementary errors '' and formulaic approach , as well as for `` Lehrer 's failure to grasp some fundamental principles of scientific thinking '' ."
"keeney","Keeney","ORG","is Chair for","be Chair for","nconnect","nConnect","ORG","Keeney is founder and Chair for nConnect , an education non-profit focused on enhancing rigorous high school science and math programs ."
