"subject_str","subject_id","subject_type","predicate_org","predicate","object_str","object_id","object_type","text"
"robert a. millikan","Robert A. Millikan","PERSON","is president of","be president of","caltech","Caltech","ORG","Einstein next traveled to California , where he met Caltech president and Nobel laureate Robert A. Millikan ."
"einstein","http://www.wikidata.org/entity/Q937","Person","was visiting","be visit","the united states","http://www.wikidata.org/entity/Q30","Country","In 1933 , while Einstein was visiting the United States , Adolf Hitler came to power in Germany ."
"adolf hitler","Adolf Hitler","PERSON","is new chancellor from","be new chancellor from","germany","Germany","GPE","In February 1933 , while on a visit to the United States , Einstein knew he could not return to Germany with the rise to power of the Nazis under Germany 's new chancellor , Adolf Hitler ."
"einstein","Einstein","PERSON","visited","visit","america","http://www.wikidata.org/entity/Q30","Country","In December 1930 , Einstein visited America for the second time , originally intended as a two-month working visit as a research fellow at the California Institute of Technology ."
"walter isaacson","Walter Isaacson","PERSON","is biographer of","be biographer of","einstein","Einstein","PERSON","Walter Isaacson , Einstein 's biographer , described this as `` one of the most memorable scenes in the new era of celebrity '' ."
"adolf hitler","Adolf Hitler","PERSON","is new chancellor from","be new chancellor from","germany","http://www.wikidata.org/entity/Q41304","Country","In February 1933 , while on a visit to the United States , Einstein knew he could not return to Germany with the rise to power of the Nazis under Germany 's new chancellor , Adolf Hitler ."
"eduard","Eduard","PERSON","is son of","be son of","einstein","Einstein","ORG","Einstein 's son Eduard had a breakdown at about age 20 and was diagnosed with schizophrenia ."
"marie winteler","Marie Winteler","PERSON","was","be","a year older","a year older","DATE","Marie Winteler , who was a year older , moved to Olsberg , Switzerland , for a teaching post ."
"einstein","http://www.wikidata.org/entity/Q937","Person","was visiting","be visit","the united states","the United States","GPE","In 1933 , while Einstein was visiting the United States , Adolf Hitler came to power in Germany ."
"eduard","Eduard","PERSON","is son of","be son of","einstein","http://www.wikidata.org/entity/Q937","Person","Einstein 's son Eduard had a breakdown at about age 20 and was diagnosed with schizophrenia ."
"einstein","http://www.wikidata.org/entity/Q937","Person","visited","visit","america","America","GPE","In December 1930 , Einstein visited America for the second time , originally intended as a two-month working visit as a research fellow at the California Institute of Technology ."
"world war i","World War I","EVENT","broke out","break out","that year","that year","DATE","As World War I broke out that year , the plan for Kaiser Wilhelm Institute for Physics was aborted ."
"einstein","Einstein","PERSON","visited","visit","america","America","GPE","In December 1930 , Einstein visited America for the second time , originally intended as a two-month working visit as a research fellow at the California Institute of Technology ."
"harry emerson fosdick","Harry Emerson Fosdick","PERSON","is pastor at","be pastor at","new york","New York","GPE","Harry Emerson Fosdick , pastor at New York 's Riverside Church , gave Einstein a tour of the church and showed him a full-size statue that the church made of Einstein , standing at the entrance ."
"einstein","Einstein","ORG","was visiting","be visit","the united states","http://www.wikidata.org/entity/Q30","Country","In 1933 , while Einstein was visiting the United States , Adolf Hitler came to power in Germany ."
"einstein","Einstein","PERSON","was visiting","be visit","the united states","the United States","GPE","In 1933 , while Einstein was visiting the United States , Adolf Hitler came to power in Germany ."
"walter isaacson","Walter Isaacson","PERSON","is biographer of","be biographer of","einstein","http://www.wikidata.org/entity/Q937","Person","Walter Isaacson , Einstein 's biographer , described this as `` one of the most memorable scenes in the new era of celebrity '' ."
"einstein","Einstein","ORG","visited","visit","america","http://www.wikidata.org/entity/Q30","Country","In December 1930 , Einstein visited America for the second time , originally intended as a two-month working visit as a research fellow at the California Institute of Technology ."
"robert a. millikan","Robert A. Millikan","PERSON","is president of","be president of","caltech","http://www.wikidata.org/entity/Q161562","Language","Einstein next traveled to California , where he met Caltech president and Nobel laureate Robert A. Millikan ."
"eduard","Eduard","PERSON","is son of","be son of","einstein","Einstein","PERSON","Einstein 's son Eduard had a breakdown at about age 20 and was diagnosed with schizophrenia ."
"wilfrid israel","Wilfrid Israel","GPE","visiting","visit","india","http://www.wikidata.org/entity/Q668","Country","Sundaram was Gandhi 's disciple and special envoy , whom Wilfrid Israel met while visiting India and visiting the Indian leader 's home in 1925 ."
"wilfrid israel","Wilfrid Israel","GPE","visiting","visit","india","India","GPE","Sundaram was Gandhi 's disciple and special envoy , whom Wilfrid Israel met while visiting India and visiting the Indian leader 's home in 1925 ."
"einstein","Einstein","ORG","visited","visit","america","America","GPE","In December 1930 , Einstein visited America for the second time , originally intended as a two-month working visit as a research fellow at the California Institute of Technology ."
"walter isaacson","Walter Isaacson","PERSON","is biographer of","be biographer of","einstein","Einstein","ORG","Walter Isaacson , Einstein 's biographer , described this as `` one of the most memorable scenes in the new era of celebrity '' ."
"einstein","http://www.wikidata.org/entity/Q937","Person","visited","visit","america","http://www.wikidata.org/entity/Q30","Country","In December 1930 , Einstein visited America for the second time , originally intended as a two-month working visit as a research fellow at the California Institute of Technology ."
"wilfrid israel","Wilfrid Israel","PERSON","visiting","visit","india","http://www.wikidata.org/entity/Q668","Country","Sundaram was Gandhi 's disciple and special envoy , whom Wilfrid Israel met while visiting India and visiting the Indian leader 's home in 1925 ."
"wilfrid israel","Wilfrid Israel","PERSON","visiting","visit","india","India","GPE","Sundaram was Gandhi 's disciple and special envoy , whom Wilfrid Israel met while visiting India and visiting the Indian leader 's home in 1925 ."
"einstein","Einstein","ORG","was visiting","be visit","the united states","the United States","GPE","In 1933 , while Einstein was visiting the United States , Adolf Hitler came to power in Germany ."
"adolf hitler","Adolf Hitler","PERSON","is new chancellor from","be new chancellor from","germany","http://www.wikidata.org/entity/Q183","Country","In February 1933 , while on a visit to the United States , Einstein knew he could not return to Germany with the rise to power of the Nazis under Germany 's new chancellor , Adolf Hitler ."
"carl laemmle","Carl Laemmle","PERSON","is head of","be head of","universal studios","Universal Studios","ORG","Carl Laemmle , head of Universal Studios , gave Einstein a tour of his studio and introduced him to Chaplin ."
"einstein","Einstein","PERSON","was visiting","be visit","the united states","http://www.wikidata.org/entity/Q30","Country","In 1933 , while Einstein was visiting the United States , Adolf Hitler came to power in Germany ."
