"subject_str","subject_id","subject_type","predicate_org","predicate","object_str","object_id","object_type","text"
"the kyrgyz republic","The Kyrgyz Republic","GPE","to sign","to sign","the collective security treaty","the Collective Security Treaty","LAW","The Kyrgyz Republic was a co-founder of the Shanghai Cooperation Organisation ( SCO ) and the Commonwealth of Independent States ( CIS ) , one of the first countries to sign the Collective Security Treaty ( CST ) ."
"calhoun","Calhoun","PERSON","is","be","the social sciences","the Social Sciences","ORG","The making and remaking of connections changes the connected parties ( whether these are individuals or formal organizations or solidarities at various scales ) .Craig CALHOUN is Professor of the Social Sciences at New York University and is the founding director of NYUs Institute for Public Knowledge ."
"the ends of history","the Ends of History","WORK_OF_ART",": Exploring",": Exploring","hegel","Hegel","PERSON","Multicultural Dynamics and the Ends of History : Exploring Kant , Hegel , and Marx ."
"hindus","Hindus","NORP","organized a major conference to position","organize a major conference to position","the vishwa hindu parishad","the Vishwa Hindu Parishad","ORG","In 1985 , Hindus organized a major conference to position the Vishwa Hindu Parishad ( World Hindu Council ) as the umbrella organization for Hinduism in Denmark ."
"george ryan","George Ryan","PERSON","is Governor a Republican from","be Governor a Republican from","illinois","Illinois","GPE","On January 11 , 2003 , Illinois Governor George Ryan -- a Republican on record as saying that `` some crimes are so horrendous ... that society has a right to demand the ultimate penalty '' -- Commuted the capital sentences of all 167 prisoners on his state 's death row ."
"alexander lukashenko","Alexander Lukashenko","PERSON","is president of","be president of","belarussian","Belarussian","NORP","View that the introduction of capitalism in the independent Belarus severely damaged the economy , both agricultural and industrial , that had flourished , 1945-89 ; focus on the career and policies of the first Belarussian president , Alexander Lukashenko , elected in 1994 ."
"ronald reagan","Ronald Reagan","PERSON","to drop","to drop","marcos","Marcos","PERSON","In a 1985-86 crisis , communism 's lack of credibility allowed Ronald Reagan to drop Marcos and permit democracy . ["
"harold wilson","Harold Wilson","PERSON","is Prime Minister from","be Prime Minister from","gb","GB","ORG","This article investigates the claim of GB 's Prime Minister , Harold Wilson , to have `` killed '' the Multilateral Force ( MLF ) , an attempt to bring about nuclear sharing within the North Atlantic Treaty Organization ( NATO ) & answer the supposed German desire for equality of status ."
"enrico berlinguer","Enrico Berlinguer","PERSON","is Secretary of","be Secretary of","pci","PCI","ORG","When the Central Committee of the Italian Communist Party met in February , 1973 , PCI Secretary Enrico Berlinguer reported that `` membership in the party and , to a less satisfactory extent , in the Youth Federation ( FGCI ) , shows a constant increase . ''"
"shell","Shell","ORG","commissioned ERM to conduct","commission ERM to conduct","the eia rectification process","the EIA Rectification Process","ORG","Shell commissioned ERM , an independent consultancy , to conduct the EIA Rectification Process ."
"beaumont","Beaumont","PERSON","warned","warn","nearly 200 years ago","nearly 200 years ago","DATE","Tocqueville and Beaumont warned nearly 200 years ago : While society in the United States gives the example of the most extended liberty , the prisons of the same country offer the spectacle of the most complete despotism ( 1979 , 79 ) ."
"china","China","GPE","is neighbors of","be neighbor of","japan","Japan","GPE","This special issue highlights one of the important subjects of this journal , Japanese politics and international relations , as studied in Japan 's neighbors , Korea and China , and Japan itself ."
"200","200","CARDINAL","foremost","foremost","nigerians","Nigerians","NORP","2000 foremost Nigerians ."
"congress","Congress","ORG","remade the postuWorld War II national security infrastructure creating","remake the postuWorld War II national security infrastructure create","the office of the director of national intelligence","the Office of the Director of National Intelligence","ORG","In the midst of the 2004 presidential election , Congress and the president remade the postuWorld War II national security infrastructure in less than five months , creating the Office of the Director of National Intelligence ( DNI ) and a National Counterterrorism Center ( NCTC ) ."
"alderman edward marston","Alderman Edward Marston","PERSON","leader of","leader of","leicester city council","Leicester City Council","ORG","local organiser on resettlement board ; and Alderman Edward Marston , leader of Leicester City Council ."
"miyatake gaikotsu","Miyatake Gaikotsu","PERSON","is the editor of","be the editor of","democracy","Democracy","ORG","Miyatake Gaikotsu , the editor of Democracy in 1919 , outlined the benefits that democratic reforms might provide in a post-World War I world ."
"tocqueville","Tocqueville","PERSON","warned","warn","nearly 200 years ago","nearly 200 years ago","DATE","Tocqueville and Beaumont warned nearly 200 years ago : While society in the United States gives the example of the most extended liberty , the prisons of the same country offer the spectacle of the most complete despotism ( 1979 , 79 ) ."
"islam","Islam","ORG","the case of","the case of","morocco","Morocco","GPE","Transnationalism , Islam , and nation-building : the case of Turkey and Morocco ."
"pinkowitz","Pinkowitz","PERSON","thank","thank","the capital markets","the Capital Markets","ORG","Pinkowitz and Williamson thank the Capital Markets"
"george clinton","George Clinton","PERSON","is first Governor of","be 1 Governor of","new york","New York","GPE","Public papers of George Clinton , first Governor of New York , 1777-1795 , 1801-1804 ."
"mexico","Mexico","GPE","'S","'S","pri","PRI","ORG","ELECTORAL `` MANAGEMENT `` OF OPPOSITION PARTIES BY MEXICO 'S PRI , 1970-1994 : A PRELIMINARY MODEL OF DYNAMIC PREEMPTIVE AND REACTIVE STRATEGIES ."
"east london","East London","GPE","The case","The case","newham","Newham","GPE","Community and prosperity beyond social capital : The case of Newham , East London ."
"russell a. alger","Russell A. Alger","PERSON","is Secretary of","be Secretary of","war","War","ORG","Letter , Russell A. Alger , Secretary of War , to Albion Winegar Tourgee , 1897-03-15 , acknowledging Tourgee 's request to take up the matter with the President of the United States , possibly Tourgee 's consul appointment ."
"morley","Morley","PERSON","is bishop of","be bishop of","winchester","Winchester","GPE","Including some account of the fortunes of Morley , bishop of Winchester , his first patron , and the friend of Isaak Walton ."
"calhoun","Calhoun","PERSON","of","of","the social sciences","the Social Sciences","ORG","The making and remaking of connections changes the connected parties ( whether these are individuals or formal organizations or solidarities at various scales ) .Craig CALHOUN is Professor of the Social Sciences at New York University and is the founding director of NYUs Institute for Public Knowledge ."
"the united states","the United States","GPE","prepares to exit","prepare to exit","afghanistan","Afghanistan","GPE","As the United States prepares to exit Afghanistan , it is focusing too much on security , overlooking the political elements of the transition , write two former senior U.S. officials ."
"charles taylor","Charles Taylor","PERSON","vs","vs","john gray","John Gray","PERSON","Liberals and Pluralists : Charles Taylor vs John Gray ."
"the american voter revisited","The American Voter Revisited","WORK_OF_ART","re-created","re - create","the american voter","The American Voter","WORK_OF_ART","The American Voter Revisited , 2008b ) re-created The American Voter using contemporary data ."
"big data","Big Data","ORG","is Scaling","be Scaling","business intelligence","Business Intelligence","ORG","A Comparative Study on How Big Data is Scaling Business Intelligence and Analytics ."
"islam","Islam","ORG","the case of","the case of","turkey","Turkey","GPE","Transnationalism , Islam , and nation-building : the case of Turkey and Morocco ."
"jim clifton","Jim Clifton","PERSON","is chairman of","be chairman of","gallup","Gallup","ORG","Gallup chairman and CEO Jim Clifton presents his perspective on current global employment and job creation issues , how these affect society in general , and his recommendations for creating good jobs"
"gwp","GWP","ORG","to foster","to foster","integrated water resources management","Integrated Water Resources Management","ORG","GWP was created to foster Integrated Water Resources Management ( IWRM ) , which aims to ensure the co-ordinated development and management of water , land , and related resources by maximising economic and social welfare without compromising the sustainability of vital environmental systems ."
"1940-2004","1940-2004","DATE","is senior editor of","be senior editor of","telos","Telos","ORG","Eulogizes Piccone ( 1940-2004 ) , senior editor of Telos , referring to him as the engine for the evolution of intellectual exchange following the collapse of the New Left ."
"conflicts","Q185407","War","roil","roil","the bear river","The Bear River","LOC","Damn the dams : conflicts roil the Bear River -- 7 ."
"germany","Germany","GPE","should support","should support","turkey","Turkey","GPE","Germany and its European partners should support Turkey in maintaining and improving services to Syrian refugees in Turkey , and in delivering aid more effectively to internally displaced persons ( IDPs ) inside Syria ."
"calhoun","Calhoun","PERSON","is Professor of","be Professor of","the social sciences","the Social Sciences","ORG","The making and remaking of connections changes the connected parties ( whether these are individuals or formal organizations or solidarities at various scales ) .Craig CALHOUN is Professor of the Social Sciences at New York University and is the founding director of NYUs Institute for Public Knowledge ."
"the bcg matrix","The BCG Matrix","PRODUCT","was introduced","be introduce","almost 50 years ago","almost 50 years ago","DATE","The BCG Matrix was introduced almost 50 years ago , and is today considered one of the most iconic strategic planning techniques ."
"korallgrottan","Korallgrottan","GPE","covering","cover","the last 4000 years","the last 4000 years","DATE","The 18O record of a stalagmite from Korallgrottan covering the last 4000 years agrees with the concept of a warmer period , the so called Medieval Warm Period , centred around AD1000 and a colder period , the so called Little Ice Age , somewhere between AD1000 and today ."
"jim clifton","Jim Clifton","PERSON","is CEO of","be CEO of","gallup","Gallup","ORG","Gallup chairman and CEO Jim Clifton presents his perspective on current global employment and job creation issues , how these affect society in general , and his recommendations for creating good jobs"
"gamal","Gamal","PERSON","is son of","be son of","mubarak","Mubarak","PERSON","Mubarak 's son , Gamal , has entered politics & speaks publicly about introducing reforms but is unlikely to promote multiparty competition unless pressured by the electorate ."
"the soviet union","the Soviet Union","GPE","joined the US to terminate","join the US to terminate","the cold war","Q8683","War","The Report made clear that the success of the military pillar made detente possible , and when the Soviet Union joined the US a decade later to terminate the Cold War , they were , in effect , responding to the Harmel Report 's message ."
"duane a. smith","Duane A. Smith","PERSON","is author of","be author of","horace tabor","Horace Tabor","PERSON","Now Duane A. Smith , author of Horace Tabor : His Life and the Legend , rescues this larger-than-life figure from obscurity in this new and definitive biography of the Central City lawyer turned Colorado senator ."
"lobbyists","Lobbyists","ORG","must observe","must observe","the lobbyists code of conduct","the Lobbyists Code of Conduct","LAW","Lobbyists must file returns with the Commissioner of Lobbying and observe the Lobbyists Code of Conduct ."
"gwp","GWP","ORG","promotes","promote","iwrm","IWRM","ORG","GWP promotes IWRM by creating fora at global , regional , and national levels , designed to support stakeholders in the practical implementation of IWRM ."
"essington lewis","Essington Lewis","PERSON","visited","visit","japan","Japan","GPE","The following article traces the origins of the iron ore embargo back to 1934 when Essington Lewis , the Managing Director of the Broken Hill Proprietary Company Ltd ( BHP ) , Australia 's iron and steel monopoly , visited Japan and subsequently advocated the development of an Australian armaments industry to counter probable Japanese aggression in the Pacific ."
"the bcg matrix","the BCG Matrix","ORG","was introduced","be introduce","almost 50 years ago","almost 50 years ago","DATE","The BCG Matrix was introduced almost 50 years ago , and is today considered one of the most iconic strategic planning techniques ."
"the ends of history","the Ends of History","WORK_OF_ART",": Exploring",": Exploring","marx","Marx","PERSON","Multicultural Dynamics and the Ends of History : Exploring Kant , Hegel , and Marx ."
"hamas","Hamas","ORG","rules","rule","gaza","Gaza","GPE","Hamas rules Gaza and the lives of the two million Palestinians who live there ."
"andrei lukanov","Andrei Lukanov","PERSON","is Prime Minister of","be Prime Minister of","bulgaria","Bulgaria","GPE","Bulgaria 's Prime Minister , Andrei Lukanov , elected in June 1990 , resigned on 29 November 1990 ."
"belgium","Belgium","GPE","of","of","moroccan","Moroccan","NORP","Corridor report on Belgium : the case of Moroccan and Turkish immigrants ."
"congress","Congress","ORG","remade the postuWorld War II national security infrastructure creating","remake the postuWorld War II national security infrastructure create","a national counterterrorism center","a National Counterterrorism Center","ORG","In the midst of the 2004 presidential election , Congress and the president remade the postuWorld War II national security infrastructure in less than five months , creating the Office of the Director of National Intelligence ( DNI ) and a National Counterterrorism Center ( NCTC ) ."
"ronald j. kostraba","Ronald J. Kostraba","PERSON","is  of","be   of","parklawn conference center","Parklawn Conference Center","ORG","Exhibited : `` Images from the History of the Public Health Service , '' organized by Ronald J. Kostraba , Parklawn Conference Center , 1989. ;"
"samora machel","Samora Machel","PERSON","is president of","be president of","frelimo","FRELIMO","ORG","Liberation of women , '' reads an oft-quoted statement of Samora Machel , FRELIMO president , `` is a fundamental necessity for our revolution ; a guarantee of its continuity and a precondition for victory . ''"
"huey p. newton","Huey P. Newton","PERSON","is the founder of","be the founder of","the black panther party","the Black Panther Party","ORG","His involvement in a plan to kill a witness who was testifying against Huey P. Newton , the founder of the Black Panther Party , had led to his incarceration ."
"southdiv","SOUTHDIV","ORG","has created","have create","the design build order contract","the Design Build Order Contract","PRODUCT","SOUTHDIV has created the Design Build Order Contract ( DBOC ) , which is a hybrid of the indefinite quantities ( IDQ ) contract and the two phase design build contract ."
"ahmad yasafi","Ahmad Yasafi","PERSON","is a Sufi of16th","be a Sufi of16th","17th century","17th century","DATE","And one of the Sufis whosehagiography has become an important subject of study is that of Ahmad Yasafi , a Sufi of16th 17th century ."
"the commissioner of lobbying","the Commissioner of Lobbying","LAW","to develop","to develop","a lobbyists code of conduct","a Lobbyists Code of Conduct","LAW","The Commissioner of Lobbying is required to develop a Lobbyists Code of Conduct ."
"parlamentos","Parlamentos","GPE","por","por","el ministerio de ciencia y tecnologia espanol","el Ministerio de Ciencia y Tecnologia Espanol","ORG","Asociado al Proyecto de Investigacion BJU2003-05935 : Parlamentos y Ciudades en la Corona de Aragon , financiado por el Ministerio de Ciencia y Tecnologia Espanol ; Fondos FEDER ."
"hayek","Hayek","PERSON","on","on","spontaneous order","Spontaneous Order","WORK_OF_ART","Hayek on Spontaneous Order and Constitutional Design ."
"daniel ellsberg","Daniel Ellsberg","PERSON","is the Snowden of","be the Snowden of","the 1960s","the 1960s","DATE","In the winter of 2014 , Arundhati Roy met Edward Snowden , along with the actor and writer John Cusack and Daniel Ellsberg , the Snowden of the 1960s ."
"holland","Holland","PERSON","is  of","be   of","henry edward","Henry Edward","PERSON","by his son , Henry Edward lord Holland ."
"peer","Peer","ORG","reviewed","review","postprint","Postprint","PERSON","Peer reviewed ; Postprint"
"mainland china","Mainland China","GPE","frames","frame","taiwan","Taiwan","GPE","Mainland China frames Taiwan : how China 's news websites covered Taiwan 's presidential elections ."
"belgrade","Belgrade","GPE","need","need","heat health warning system","Heat Health Warning System","LAW","Does Belgrade ( Serbia ) need heat health warning system ? ."
"calhoun","Calhoun","PERSON","Professor of","Professor of","the social sciences","the Social Sciences","ORG","The making and remaking of connections changes the connected parties ( whether these are individuals or formal organizations or solidarities at various scales ) .Craig CALHOUN is Professor of the Social Sciences at New York University and is the founding director of NYUs Institute for Public Knowledge ."
"japan","Japan","GPE","colonized","colonize","taiwan","Taiwan","GPE","AbstractFor the history connecting East Asia with the West , there is much literature about contact and trade across the Atlantic Ocean from the sixteenth to the early nineteenth centuries.1 This paper notes the rapid growth of the Pacific Ocean in linking Asia with the larger world in the early twentieth century by perceiving the economic relationships between Taiwan and Hong Kong while Japan colonized Taiwan ."
"east london","East London","GPE","case","case","newham","Newham","GPE","Community and prosperity beyond social capital : The case of Newham , East London ."
"four fifths","four fifths","CARDINAL","get","get","one fifth","one fifth","CARDINAL","Wealth is asymmetrically distributed ; approximately one fifth of the world ( the G 7 nations ) produces and consumes four fifths of goods and services ; four fifths ( the G 77 nations ) get one fifth ."
"george marshall","George Marshall","PERSON","is Secretary of of","be Secretary of of","state","State","ORG","Sixty years ago Secretary of State George Marshall revolutionized American foreign policy when he called on the United States to come to the aid of war-torn Europe ."
"the european community","the European Community","ORG","has attempted to reform","have attempt to reform","the common agriculture policy","the Common Agriculture Policy","LAW","Since the beginning of the General Agreement of Tariffs and Trade Uruguay Round , the European Community has twice attempted to reform the Common Agriculture Policy , resulting in the February 1988 stabilizers reform package and May 1992 MacSharry reform package ."
"sverre lodgaard","Sverre Lodgaard","PERSON","is is a Senior Research Fellow at","be be a Senior Research Fellow at","the norwegian institute of international affairs","the Norwegian Institute of International Affairs","ORG","This book will be of great interest to all students of arms control , strategic studies , war and conflict studies , and IR/security studies in general Sverre Lodgaard is a Senior Research Fellow at the Norwegian Institute of International Affairs , Oslo ."
"the united states","the United States","GPE","losing","lose","turkey","Turkey","GPE","Is the United States losing Turkey ? ."
"michele field","Michele Field","PERSON","is formerly Literary Editor of","be formerly Literary Editor of","the sydney morning herald","the Sydney Morning Herald","ORG","Michele Field , formerly Literary Editor of the Sydney Morning Herald , is a freelance writer and journalist living in London ."
"jim clifton","Jim Clifton","PERSON","is chairman of","be chairman of","gallup","Gallup","ORG","Gallup chairman and CEO Jim Clifton presents his perspective on current global employment and job creation issues , how these affect society in general , and his recommendations for creating good jobs ."
"the kyrgyz republic","the Kyrgyz Republic","GPE","to sign","to sign","the collective security treaty","the Collective Security Treaty","LAW","The Kyrgyz Republic was a co-founder of the Shanghai Cooperation Organisation ( SCO ) and the Commonwealth of Independent States ( CIS ) , one of the first countries to sign the Collective Security Treaty ( CST ) ."
"conflicts","Q185407","War","roil","roil","the bear river","the Bear River","LOC","Damn the dams : conflicts roil the Bear River -- 7 ."
"ifpri","IFPRI","ORG","is a member of","be a member of","the cgiar consortium","the CGIAR Consortium","ORG","IFPRI is a member of the CGIAR Consortium ."
"paul piccone","Paul Piccone","PERSON","is Friend of","be Friend of","american","American","NORP","Our American Friend Paul Piccone was a Free Spirit and a Loud Talker ."
"flores forbes","Flores Forbes","PERSON","is a former leader in","be a former leader in","the black panther party","the Black Panther Party","ORG","Flores Forbes , a former leader in the Black Panther Party , has been free from prison for twenty-five years ."
"michiyo obi","Michiyo Obi","PERSON","is Professor of","be Professor of","faculty of policy studies","Faculty of Policy Studies","ORG","Michiyo Obi is Professor of Faculty of Policy Studies at Nanzan University , Japan ."
"china","China","GPE","Since","Since","the boxer movement","the Boxer Movement","ORG","China and the Powers Since the Boxer Movement ."
"das zweite","Das zweite","PERSON","sind die","sind die","erfahrungen","Erfahrungen","ORG","Das zweite sind die Erfahrungen , der Newcomers in Berlin ."
"sverre lodgaard","Sverre Lodgaard","PERSON","is a Senior Research Fellow at","be a Senior Research Fellow at","the norwegian institute of international affairs","the Norwegian Institute of International Affairs","ORG","This book will be of great interest to all students of arms control , strategic studies , war and conflict studies , and IR/security studies in general Sverre Lodgaard is a Senior Research Fellow at the Norwegian Institute of International Affairs , Oslo ."
"simpson","Simpson","PERSON","calls","call","permanent revolution","Permanent Revolution","ORG","In the case of the Reformation in England , the first revolution ( what Simpson calls `` permanent revolution '' ) was heady and radical ."
"jakob von uexkull","Jakob von Uexkull","PERSON","is Chair of","be Chair of","the world future council democracy","the World Future Council Democracy","ORG","Jakob von Uexkull , Chair of the World Future Council Democracy can not exist without peace ."
"williamson","Williamson","PERSON","thank","thank","the capital markets","the Capital Markets","ORG","Pinkowitz and Williamson thank the Capital Markets"
"martti ahtisaari","Martti Ahtisaari","PERSON","the former president of","the former president of","finland","Finland","GPE","In an essay I wrote for Peace Review 22.1 , I described a rather illuminating , if somewhat startling , conversation I had with Martti Ahtisaari , the former president of Finland and Nobel Peace Prize laureate , in September 2008 , just a few months after Kosovo had declared independence ."
"w. huskisson","W. Huskisson","PERSON","President of","President of","the board of trade","the Board of Trade","ORG","W. Huskisson , President of the Board of Trade ."
"the international treaty","the international treaty","LAW","protects","protect","wetlands","Wetlands","LOC","For this purpose , we examined the conservation policies of the Ramsar Convention ( the international treaty that protects wetlands ) and the European Union ( as an example of relevant continental level policy-making ) from the viewpoint of bird-mediated dispersal of aquatic organisms ."
"universidade federal","Universidade Federal","ORG","do","do","rio de janeiro","Rio de Janeiro","GPE","Universidade Federal do Rio de Janeiro ."
"sheykh kamal khatib","Sheykh Kamal Khatib","PERSON","is former deputy leader of","be former deputy leader of","imnf","IMNF","ORG","Sheykh Kamal Khatib , former deputy leader of IMNF , declared that the IMNF had been a tool to serve the Islamic project and regardless of having been outlawed , the movement `` would find a `` thousand ways '' to serve that project . ' ''"
"rokhlin","Rokhlin","PERSON","former chairman of","former chairman of","the duma defense committee","the Duma Defense Committee","ORG","Rokhlin was former chairman of the Duma Defense Committee and lead of the opposition Movement in Support of the Army , Defense Industry , and Military Science ."
"instituto de oceanologia","Instituto de Oceanologia","ORG","Fil :","Fil :","werlinger","Werlinger","GPE","Instituto de Oceanologia ; Cuba ; Fil : Werlinger , Camilo ."
"putin","Putin","PERSON","are undermining","be undermine","america","America","GPE","The plot to destroy democracy : how Putin and his spies are undermining America and dismantling the West ."
"m. jean baptist colbert","M. Jean Baptist Colbert","PERSON","Secretary of","Secretary of","state","State","ORG","The political testament of M. Jean Baptist Colbert , minister and Secretary of State wherein is contain 'd all that hath pass 'd under the reign of Lewis the XIV unto the year 1684 : with remarks upon the government of the kingdom of France / translated out of French . ;"
"morley","Morley","PERSON","is the friend of","be the friend of","isaak walton","Isaak Walton","PERSON","Including some account of the fortunes of Morley , bishop of Winchester , his first patron , and the friend of Isaak Walton ."
"primary source microfilm","Primary Source Microfilm","WORK_OF_ART","is an imprint of","be a imprint of","the gale group","the Gale Group","ORG","Digitized image of the microfilm version produced in Woodbridge , CT by Research Publications , 1982-2002 ( later known as Primary Source Microfilm , an imprint of the Gale Group ) ."
"jim clifton","Jim Clifton","PERSON","is CEO of","be CEO of","gallup","Gallup","ORG","Gallup chairman and CEO Jim Clifton presents his perspective on current global employment and job creation issues , how these affect society in general , and his recommendations for creating good jobs ."
"flexible supervision","Flexible Supervision","ORG","outperforms","outperform","mandatory supervision","Mandatory Supervision","ORG","The result that Flexible Supervision outperforms Mandatory Supervision remains robust to a series of extensions to our baseline model ."
"the soviet union","the Soviet Union","GPE","joined the US to terminate","join the US to terminate","the cold war","the Cold War","EVENT","The Report made clear that the success of the military pillar made detente possible , and when the Soviet Union joined the US a decade later to terminate the Cold War , they were , in effect , responding to the Harmel Report 's message ."
